Institute of Fisheries Analysis fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Department of Economics and Commerce records, 1960 - 1996; F-240-6; 91 cm of textual records; Department of Economics
  - Committees, 1966 - 1983; F-240-6-2; 21 cm of textual records
    - Executive Committee - Policies, 1971 - 1972; F-240-6-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
    - [Appointments Committee], 1972 - 1975; F-240-6-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
    - [Graduate Curriculum Committee], 1972 - 1977; F-240-6-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
    - [DEC - General Administration and external review], 1973 - 1975; F-240-6-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
    - Dean's Advisory Committee, 1975; F-240-6-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
    - [Planning and Priorities Committee, 1975; F-240-6-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
    - [President's Advisory Committee on University Priorities], 1983; F-240-6-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
  - Curriculum and instruction files, 1965 - 1996; F-240-6-3; 32 cm of textual records
    Records in this sub-series relate to various programs and courses developed and administered by the Department of Economics. Topics covered include course development and administration; registration; and class assignments and examinations. Documents include syllabi, correspondence, memoranda, course handouts, reading lists, bibliographies, assignment outlines, examinations, and schedules.
    - Course files, 1966 - 1996; F-240-6-3-1; 28 cm of textual records
      - [Economics 200, 280, 484, 496 - examinations, assignments, and course overview], 1966 - 1988; F-240-6-3-1-1 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - Registration - fall 1968, F-240-6-3-1-2 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - Qualifying examinations - Resource Economics, 1968 - 1979; F-240-6-3-1-3 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - Economics 101: The Canadian Economy - course administration, fall 1970, F-240-6-3-1-4 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - Economics 101: The Canadian Economy - tutorial conduct, fall 1970, F-240-6-3-1-5 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - Economics 863: Readings Course, [197-?]; F-240-6-3-1-6 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
        Creator's original file classification code: EC. 863.
      - MBA 691-5: Business and Society, fall 1970, F-240-6-3-1-7 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - MBA 691-5: Business and Society - general, 1970; F-240-6-3-1-8 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - MBA 691-5: Business and Society - course administration, fall 1970, F-240-6-3-1-9 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - MBA 691-5: Business and Society - Economic Policy mini course, fall 1970, F-240-6-3-1-10 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - MBA 691-5: Business and Society - course administration, 1970 - 1971; F-240-6-3-1-11 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - MBA 691-5: Business and Society - general, spring 1971, 1970 - 1971; F-240-6-3-1-12 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - [Economics 101 - course handouts, 1970 - 1973; F-240-6-3-1-13 (Archival box - standard 240-12)
      - Economics 101 - examinations and tests, 1970 - 1979; F-240-6-3-1-14 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
        Creator's original file classification code: EC. 101.
      - Economics 101: The Canadian Economy - course administration, spring 1971, F-240-6-3-1-15 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - MBA 691-5: Business and Society - Macro Economics mini course, spring 1971, F-240-6-3-1-16 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Course scheduling, 1972; F-240-6-3-1-17 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - examinations, 1973 - 1994; F-240-6-3-1-18 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 101: The Canadian Economy - course administration, fall 1977, F-240-6-3-1-19 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 101 - teaching assistants, fall 1977, F-240-6-3-1-20 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, fall 1977, F-240-6-3-1-21 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
        Creator's original file classification code: EC. 863 Fisheries.
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - reading list, 1977 - 1993; F-240-6-3-1-22 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course outlines, 1977 - 1994; F-240-6-3-1-23 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 101: The Canadian Economy - course administration, summer 1978, F-240-6-3-1-24 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 101: The Canadian Economy - course administration, spring 1979, F-240-6-3-1-25 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, spring 1979, F-240-6-3-1-26 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 484: Canadian Fishing Industry - course administration, spring 1980, F-240-6-3-1-27 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
        Creator's original file classification code: EC. 484.
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, spring 1980, F-240-6-3-1-28 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - General Studies 400: Individual Study Project J. Masson, 1980; F-240-6-3-1-29 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Fisheries films, 1980 - 1984; F-240-6-3-1-30 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Canadian Studies 280: Canadian Political Economy - course administration, spring 1981, F-240-6-3-1-31 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, spring 1981, F-240-6-3-1-32 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, spring 1982, F-240-6-3-1-33 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course bibliography (long), 1982 - 1983; F-240-6-3-1-34 (Archival box - standard 240-13)
      - Economics 864: Studies in Economic Fisheries Management, 1982 - 1991; F-240-6-3-1-35 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, fall 1983, F-240-6-3-1-36 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, fall 1983, F-240-6-3-1-37 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics 496: Canadian Fishing Industry - course administration, fall 1984, F-240-6-3-1-38 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
        Creator's original file classification code: EC. 496.
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, spring 1985, F-240-6-3-1-39 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, spring 1986, F-240-6-3-1-40 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, fall 1987, F-240-6-3-1-41 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Fisheries Economics comprehensive examinations, 1987 - 1993; F-240-6-3-1-42 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics 498: Directed Readings in Economic Fisheries Management, summer 1989, F-240-6-3-1-43 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, spring 1989, F-240-6-3-1-44 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - course administration, spring 1990, F-240-6-3-1-45 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Graduate courses in fisheries economics and fisheries management available at SFU (master), 1992; F-240-6-3-1-46 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - [Economics 863: Fisheries Economics - handouts], 1994; F-240-6-3-1-47 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - [Geography 251-3 - course outline], 1996; F-240-6-3-1-48 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
    - Programs and course proposals, 1965 - 1983; F-240-6-3-2; 5 cm of textual records
      - [A Proposal for Mathematical Economics in the Economics Honours and Graduate Program], [after 1965]; F-240-6-3-2-1 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - [Planned course offerings], [ca 1965] - 1983; F-240-6-3-2-2 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Economics graduate program planning, 1966; F-240-6-3-2-3 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Arts Curricula, 1966 - 1967; F-240-6-3-2-4 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - [Graduate program planning - Senate], 1967; F-240-6-3-2-5 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - [Economics program and courses - overview and proposals], 1967 - 1980; F-240-6-3-2-6 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Senate, 1968; F-240-6-3-2-7 (Archival box - standard 240-14)
      - Academic programs, 1971; F-240-6-3-2-8 (Archival box - standard 240-14)